Last boarding call for flight TF168
from Stockholm to Malmö.
But that's OK I guess.
You make my mom very happy.
-A little bit more.
-OK.
-Hold the glass.
-Wait wait wait.
Is that all I'm getting?
And let's pour some...
Oh, damn it!
OK, so it's like that today? Hey...
Happy birthday.
-Oskar?
-Hold on.
-Say something to the camera that describes Lasse.
-Damn.
My sis and her boyfriend are running late.
No, no, no. What are they doing?
-I think your mom is a bit of a slut.
-Well I think your dad is a horn dog.
-Look, it fits perfectly.
-I'll never take it off.
You promise?
Of course I promise.
Can you hold this?
I have to take the luggage.
Let's go and grab a cigarette first.
It's a bit crooked.
Come on, you little muppet.
Should I tell dad
or should you do it?
No, of course you should tell him.
It's your dad.
-I'm sorry. Could I borrow a lighter from you?
-Yes.
It's not lit.
Frida! damn, there you are. Hi.
-Have you been here for a while, or?
-No, we just got here.
Have you introduced yourselves?
-This is Mia, my sister.
-Frida.
And this is Tim, her boyfriend.
- Frida is Elisabeth's daughter.
-Oh, OK.
-Well, let's not stand here all day.
Thank you so much for that. But above all
I give my sincerest gratitude-
-for this fantastic food that
Oskar and Frida have put together.
And... I get so nervous
when I speak like this.
But it feels quite touching
that you're all here when I'm turning 60-
-and above all to celebrate that
Elisabeth and I are getting engaged.
But above all, a great thank you
to Elisabeth for saying yes.
-Well, look here. Come in. Hi.
-Hi, dad.
Another surprise. This is my daughter Mia,
this is... - Hi, Tim. - This is Tim.
This is great.
Well, now I'm just completely
surrounded by love.
And now I'm just going to sit down next to Elisabeth and relax.
And let's have a fucking good time tonight, right?
Hello.
I think the big gift just arrived.
Well, now I'm getting emotional.
Mia just told me that she and
Tim are going to get married.
Congratulations!
Hi, Mia. So good to see you.
Congratulations.
Excuse me for just interrupting like this,
but I would also like to say a few words.
I'll start with you Lasse.
We may not always agree about everything.
That's OK too I guess. But above all
you make my mom very happy.
And that's all I care about.
- And mom, you really deserve the best.
And we have in some strange way
blended together as a family very quickly.
And I am incredibly happy about that.
Where are you, Oskar?
And I hope things continue like that.
And above all that you stay as happy as you seem now.
So I would also like to propose a toast - to mom and Lasse.
Cheers!
-Hip, hip!
-Hooray! Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear Lasse
Elisabeth seems lovely.
Elisabeth is amazing.
-I know you're going to like her.
-You seem like you're well, Dad.
I'm great.
Can't we go for a walk tomorrow morning,
like we used to?
When I was little, you mean?
-What are you doing? Are you flirting with her?
-What?
-With who?
-With Frida of course. You seem to enjoy each other's company anyway.
Well, I didn't get any on the plane.
-Good morning. Is it free?
-Sure, just go in.
-Dad?
-Hey, I think they're still asleep.
Hi. Should we go for a walk then?
- Hi Tim. Thank you for yesterday.
I thought we were getting together this morning.
-Are you sulking now?
-No, I'm not sulking.
I think you're sulking.
- Tim, she's sulking, right?
She is definitely sulking. Mia sulks
when Mia doesn't get what Mia wants.
I was going to ask you to come along to Fyn tomorrow
and give us advice on a house extension.
-But I realize it's the wrong time.
-No, I would love to do it.
As long as I get some time alone with you.
We have barely seen each other yet.
Of course.
-Bye.
Guys, how about a toast?
-Cheers.
-Tim, how's the company doing?
-It's doing pretty well actually.
It's always tough the first few years,
but I think-
-with time it will go really well.
We just received a huge project.
Great, congratulations.
And when will I become a grandfather?
-Stop nagging, Dad.
-Yes, we're in no rush.
Well, don't wait too long. I don't want
to be in a home when he or she comes along.
Lasse! Time to take it down a notch, don't you think?
Thank you Elisabeth. Why should all the pressure be on me?
Frida might beat me to it.
Right?
Yes, absolutely!
-Where are you going for your honeymoon then, Mia?
-I don't know.
I haven't even found a dress yet.
So I haven't had time to think about it yet.
I was actually thinking about wearing mom's dress.
If you don't mind.
Not at all, darling.
Why would I?
-Mia is nothing like I thought.
-No?
Did you think she would be more like Oskar?
Maybe.
-Mia is more like her mother.
-Is everything OK between the two of you?
Why do you ask?
Doesn't it seem to be?
Dad really didn't like that thing
about the dress. Did you notice?
Maybe you should listen to him.
Stop filming.
I'm not up for it.
-Did you cheat?
-God, you're so curious.
-Did you?
-No, I've never cheated and I never will.
-I can't think of anything worse.
-Same here.
Especially considering how Dad's been at it.
It's like sis says. We inherited Mom's faithful genes.
-That's good.
-It feels different now that he's met Elisabeth.
-Does it?
-Sure, he's so calm.
And by the way,
you might have kids before Mia and Tim.
God, you're so sweet.
Mia is lucky to have you.
You're like, the best baby brother ever.
I'm just trying to do my job.
What do you mean, I should listen to him?
Don't you like the dress?
Honestly.
It's an ugly 70's dress.
What does it matter? What is
so important to you about that dress?
I don't know. I've always
liked it since I was little.
I've always told mom
I'm going to wear it when I get married.
I just want our wedding
to be as perfect as possible.
I just want us to be happy.
I don't want some dress or your dad to ruin that.
OK?
-I thinks she's awesome.
-I noticed. Maybe you should go instead of me.
I don't have the time. I have to work.
-Can't we buy one of those too?
-Absolutely.
OK. I'll call you
when I get there. Bye.
Oh good, it's Aston's, he's one of my students.
You can just toss it in the back.
I know it's none of my business,
but I have to ask.
Sure, just ask.
Oskar and you...
Are you together or something?
-What?
-I don't know, I just think it's a bit...
What business is it of yours? Is it the age difference?
I'm a few years older than him, is that it?
Excuse me. What business is it of mine?
We'll soon be in the same family.
Don't you think that's a bit...
No but, come on, we don't even have the same parents.
You make it sound like total inbreeding.
But I have to say - your
little brother is insanely good in bed.
-Oh my God, I don't want to hear that!
-What? But he is.
-You were joking about you and Oskar of course?
-Well, yes.
I couldn't resist teasing you.
You seem so anal.
Oh God, I'm sorry, I didn't mean...
-I didn't mean anal that way. Not "anal" anal.
-It's OK.
Oskar said it's been a while
since you've been home to visit.
-Yes, since last Christmas.
-OK.
Well, Lasse seems a bit, it feels like
he's a bit different when you're at home.
I'm sorry, it might be because I'm so anal, but
it's been a while since I felt this analysed by someone.
No God, I didn't mean to analyse.
It was...It was an observation.
You, well... I'm sorry for what happened on the ferry,
that I was so...
-Charmless?
-Yes, exactly.
Mia? Would you come out here for a moment?
Raspberry?
I was thinking about having an extension here.
Maybe a guesthouse
with a glass porch maybe?
-What do you think?
-Yes, that would probably be pretty nice.
You could build a cube there...
...with a glass porch with a view of the forest, for example.
Where is dad anyway?
He had an emergency meeting in town.
-So he's not coming?
-No. He didn't tell you?
-No.
-Well, it turned out a little weird.
I’ll go inside and start making dinner,
and you and Frida can unpack. We’ll eat soon.
Hi, this is Lasse Sundström.
Leave a message and I'll call you back. Thanks, bye.
Damn it, Dad. You can't just not show up
and leave me alone on a deserted island in the middle of nowhere.
Damn it, I don't know these people.
Thank you so bloody much!
Well. Where is Mia then?
I don't know. I can go look.
Bring a flashlight. Maybe she got lost.
She's from the city.
She was going to make a phone call.
-I know she can be difficult to get to know.
-You don't say?
Well, you'll be nice to her won't you?
I know! Here. Bring some wine and cigarettes.
Here you go.
-What do you mean, nice? I'm always nice.
-Now go.
So this is where you're hiding?
-Do you want some wine?
-Please.
Have you ever been married?
No.
The closest I ever came
was an engagement that lasted-
-for exactly 5 months,
three weeks and two days.
What happened?
I discovered I was engaged
to someone I didn't know.
-I thought I did, but I didn't.
-Did he stop turning your world upside down?
No, I don't know if I've ever
met anyone like that.
I'm not sure I would want
someone to do that to me.
Thank you.
I can't believe you seriously thought
I was together with Oskar.
-Why? I don't know you.
-No, but you're funny. I like that.
Come on, I'll show you something.
I think they should be somewhere around here.
Look.
There's more coffee, if you want.
-Hey.
-No thank you.
Yes, I was wondering if you have car rental..
OK.
So there is no other way
of getting off the island?
Yes, OK. Thanks a lot. Bye.
-Damn!
-Mia! Do you want to come fishing?
Why did you kiss me?
We can't pretend
that it didn't happen.
So. Ready to leave?
We're going swimming.
We'll be back later.
-So, you like...?
-Girls. Yes.
You didn't know?
Why did you kiss me?
I don't know.
I...I just did.
-Is this stressing you out?
-I love Tim.
I get that, but a person can be attracted to several people.
Attracted to?
You, I'm not like you.
OK.
-Are you sure?
-Of course I'm sure.
-Did something happen?
-No.
No, I'm just tired.
Hi! Good morning. Sleep well?
Let's leave then.
So. Let's see here then...
-What is this, Frida?
-Take it easy, mom.
It's a sensitive engine.
It takes a while for it to start up.
Frida how many times have I told you
to ask someone to look at this car?
I know that Mom.
But you telling me doesn't help.
It won't start because you're telling me.
We'll have to take the bus.
We'll miss the ferry if we don't.
We can make this bus if we go now.
It's just as well, we'll just walk.
56 people already RSPV'd to the e-mail about the wedding.
Have you got everything?
-Did something happen, or what?
-No.
Are you angry with me?
I like you so much, Frida.
But it's a mess right now, you understand?
I get that.
But I'm right here.
You can talk to me.
Frida, I love Tim.
I don't believe that.
We have a whole life together.
I know you feel something for me.
I'm going to marry Tim in a few months.
I can't feel this way about you, don't you get that?
It's impossible.
Then I guess you'll have to stay with him.
OK... I just wanted you to get to know each other.
It may have been stupid.
I'm here to see you, Dad.
I wanted to show you what I've been doing at work.
-Talk to you about the wedding. Don't you see I need to do that?
-Sure, just talk.
Can't you focus on that?
Pull it tighter.
Come on, pull it.
Come on! Harder!
Are you still serious about wearing Mom's dress to the wedding?
The most important day of your life?
-If it's meant as a gibe at me I don't think it's worth it.
-What are you talking about?
I know you think it's my fault that Mom and I got divorced.
But we were both in it.
Yes. But only one of you was fucking her best friend
and lying about it! Right?
Why do you always have to take her side?
We had problems long before that.
OK. What does that have to do with the dress?
Why do you think it's a gibe?
-Listen. Me being unfaithful...
-I don't want to hear about your fucking infidelity, don't you get it?!
-OK, I get it, I get it.
-Hasn't it done enough damage to this family already?
I get it.
Should we put up the net now or what?
-Are we playing or not?
-No!
-I did this for your sake.
-Hey! Time to eat!
Yes!
Pull a bit harder now!
I think it was damn selfish of you to just not show up out at the cottage.
-This damn nagging.
-Nagging?
But you get along so well with Frida...
Can I have the salad? Thank you.
-Anyone want some bread?
-Thank you, I'm good.
-Mia, did you tell them we're looking for a house?
-That's nice. What a great investment.
Well, we've been looking for something small.
Maybe to expand later.
-Well, we've been looking for something small
-Eh, no...
We looked at a few places,
but there hasn't been anything that interesting.
I can't, I...
I can't...
...stay here. I had a kebab
earlier and I don't feel well.
-I'll take the car I think. Home.
-Kebab? When did you start eating meat?
No, it was one of these...
It was...a vegetarian kebab.
-A vebab.
-A vebab?
-Exactly.
-What's that? Isn't meat the point of kebab?
-Or tofu.
-That doesn't sound good at all.
But Frida, you've had lots of wine.
We'll call you a taxi.
-I can drive you.
-It's OK...
Why would you stuff yourself with vebab when you're not craving meat?
It's stuff like that I don't get.
No, well... You don't always get everything Lasse.
Hello?
Hi!
God, I missed you.
I made dinner. Come on.
What is it? Did I misunderstand
about the dress?
What?
Did something happen?
Is everything OK between you and Tim?
Did you have a fight?
Mom and I also fought a lot
when we were about to get married.
It's nerves.
It's nothing, Dad.
It's just...
Can't you tell me what's going on?
I'm just a bit tired.
Hey, tomorrow...
...why don't you show me your drafts.
And we can spend all day together.
Would you like that?
-Hi.
-What are you doing?
-I'm going home with you.
-Home?
-I thought you were staying for a week?
-Yes, but I changed my mind.
Coming back home really isn't your thing, is it.
Aren't you bringing her flower inside?
She gave you such a lovely vase.
It's not a flower.
It's an orchid.
And it's been standing here
for 30 years, Elisabeth.
You know, if you spent half as much time
caring about your family as you do your orchids-
-things would probably be different.
-Maybe you should say goodbye to Oskar?
-Ssh! I just want to go home.
God, it feels so good to be home!
If I ever want to go back,
remind me of this trip.
What happened there?
I ran into a branch on the island.
City kid, you know.
-I need to go to the office for a bit now.
-No, don't bother. Take care of it tomorrow.
What is it?
I love you.
I love you, Tim.
Plastic headboards. We'd need to do something
about these floors, I think.
A fireplace.
-I've always wanted one.
-It would be nice in winter.
-But Jakobsberg?
-What's wrong with Jakobsberg?
It's so dull out there.
We would have to redo the whole floor.
And when you get pregnant,
we won't even have room for a nursery.
"When I get pregnant". That could take ages.
Not if you stop taking birth control.
It would take a year to a year and a half.
-What do you mean, I don't want kids now. You know that.
-Maybe not now now.
But in the near future.
You do want kids with me?
We are getting married, right?
-If we're having kids, then that requires planning!
-Tim you can't plan everything. It doesn't work that way.
Well then, how do things work?
Explain to me how things work!
Hey, I'm sorry about yesterday.
You're right.
It makes me panic when you're deciding everything.
Can't you see how stressful it is?
-Well, you need someone to keep you in line.
-What did you say?
Check out Oskar.
He's coming here on Thursday.
He's grown some kind of mustache.
He looks insane. He looks like a psychopath, doesn't he?
This is Tim.
Frida?
It's very empty and lonely here.
Can't you come over here?
I'm coming. I'm coming.
No...
-What?
-Well... I don't know.
It's like you've been on another planet these past two weeks.
I barely recognize you.
What is it?
I will leave you alone.
-You want come over for dinner with us tonight?
-Eh, I can't.
How come you never come over for dinner anymore?
-Did something happen?
-No.
-But, Frida, what's going on?
-Well, I don't know how to say this.
-Me and Mia, we...
-Mia?
Something happened
between her and me.
Something?
Please try to explain, would you.
I think Mia is bisexual,
but I don't think she wants to see it that way.
And what the hell is that supposed to mean?
That I'm in love with her.
Oh dear lord!
I asked you to be nice to her,
not fall in love with her!
-Well then I misunderstood you completely because falling in love with her was my plan all along.
-How the hell can you be joking about something like this?
You can love whoever you want,
but not Lasse's daughter, do you get it?
-Anyone, but not her!
-What am I supposed to do? I'm not exactly proud of myself right now.
-And Elin?
-She doesn't know, but she gets it.
After you've been put through the exact same thing yourself.
Maybe you remember how devastated you were?
And now you're putting Elin through the exact same thing.
Damn that's low, Frida.
-What were you thinking?
-I haven't been thinking.
No, you haven't been.
No...
No, I've never cheated and I never will.
I can't think of anything worse.
Are you at home?
I waited for you for over an hour.
I'm sorry, I got late.
I missed you.
What is it?
-I can't.
-What?
What...?
I hate doing this to you so much.
Who is it?
It's Mia, Oskar's sister.
It must be hard for Lasse having two dykes in the family.
Since he's had such a hard time with us.
I'm in love with her.
So you've been cheating on me with Mia,
who is getting married to her boyfriend.
What the hell are you doing?
Well, I really don't want to do this to you.
I know exactly what you're feeling right now.
I understand.
You know what the most disgusting part is?
I really thought you were better than this.
You're just an experiment to her.
She's never going to leave him.
Do you get that?
Yes. It's... Someone was hung over
when they treaded this.
Give me the glass!
Now tell me about the mustache.
It's some kind of age crisis?
I don't know, it just happened.
Tim was totally freaked out.
He said I had to shave it off
if I wanted to be his best man.
Can I kidnap him this weekend?
Drag him to the archipelago. A bachelor's party or something.
Sure, do that.
-Have you heard from dad by the way?
-Yes, everything's fine.
-You haven't heard from him?
-No.
OK.
I'm meant to say hi from Frida by the way.
She's here this weekend with her school.
She's doing a concert at Östra Real.
You can hang out then. It's cool.
-I talked to Frida.
-Hm. She's all good?
-Not really actually.
-Oh.
-She is in love with your daughter.
-What did you say?
-Come again?
-From what I gather, Mia has feelings for Frida too.
-But Mia is engaged to Tim.
-Of course I know that, but...
-So maybe she's bisexual.
-No, I don't think so.
-Let's eat now. Sit down.
-Are you kidding?
Haricot verts?
So it's OK that my daughter is gay,
but not Mia?
My daughter is not homosexual,
Elisabeth.
-Maybe you think it's wrong, maybe you think it's a bit disgusting?
-Did I say that?
-But it's not completely normal, right?
-No, it's not completely fucking normal, is it?
No parents really want their child to be gay or lesbian,
if we're being honest, Elisabeth.
So Frida isn't normal?
Lasse when Frida came out...
...it wasn't easy, I admit.
But today I'm very happy that she is who she is.
That she stands up for who she is.
She wouldn't be my daughter otherwise.
Let's not talk about this anymore. OK?
How would that solve anything?
Lasse?
This is completely insane!
Who the hell are you, really?
What the hell are you thinking right now?
No, God damn it!
Mia?
I shouldn't have come. I have to...I have to go.
Oskar couldn't make it, but he says hi.
Wait, wait, wait, wait...
Just give me five minutes, I'll send
the kids home with their parents.
Wait for me.
Don't go.
I'm so happy you're here.
Did you hide here, or what?
I want to go away with you.
Far away.
Do you want to?
I think you've been lying a little bit to me.
I'm hardly your first girl.
No. Can you tell?
Yes, you could say that.
I thought about it on Fyn too.
Why haven't you told me?
-Are you ashamed?
-No.
I just didn't think I would feel like this again.
Were you in love with her?
-Will it make you jealous if I say yes?
-Eh, yes. Absolutely.
-Does Tim know?
-No.
It was much earlier.
I've never cheated on him.
Until now.
I want to be with you all the time.
I don't want to be just someone you cheat on Tim with.
If I had the choice, I would build a house somewhere by the ocean.
Andalusia.
Or Catalonia.
-I could live with you in a shoe box.
-Seriously?
What if we did.
Just take off, you and me.
And start over somewhere else.
Why can't we start over here?
Is that too realistic for you?
Not romantic enough?
But, Frida...
Frida.
I've never felt as strongly about anyone as I do about you in my entire life.
But you just want to run away all the time.
Start over?
Do you know how much I'd want to do that.
But you're getting married to Tim in three months.
I am so stupid.
What are you doing?
Do you love him?
You can't marry Tim.
I won't be able to handle that.
-Dad, did something happen?
-No, I just wanted to hear your voice.
And...say thank you for the vase I got.
I'm not sure I did.
OK. You're welcome.
-Are you OK??
-Yes, I'm fine.
I woke you up didn't I? I didn't realize
it was this late.
-Let's hang up.
-OK.
Fine.
-Bye then.
-Bye.
We could live like this, couldn't we?
This is almost like a shoe box.
I wouldn't want to live like this.
It's not real.
Shutting ourselves in a room miles away from everything.
It's hard for me, Frida.
I'm not as brave as you.
I just wish we didn't have to be questioned.
I want them to ask.
I'm proud of you.
I want to show everyone how much I like you.
-One o'clock at Mosebacke, then.
-Yes.
Hey.
I don't get any stubble, just some stuff.
I thought it looked OK.
-I think I've known that about Mia the whole time.
-What?
Yes, even though it only was suspicions
I had a hard time dealing with it.
You know, when Frida told me...
...I remember thinking, in a state of panic,
about everything I would miss out on.
You know, wedding, becoming a grandmother,
all those things.
But, hey...now I know better.
Yes.
I just want her to be fine.
-I'm going to the city to take care of some things.
-Now? We're leaving soon.
-What?
-To the church. You're the one who booked the meeting with the pastor at one.
Well, well, you're nervous now, aren't you?
Wedding ceremonies are actually over really quickly.
So I want you to really cherish the moment when you're up here with me.
It goes like this:
first you say your vows to each other.
then I turn to you Tim.
And your full name.
-Tim Aaron Bratthall.
-Tim Aaron, nice name, Bratthall.
-Do you take this...
-Maria.
You'll have to raise your voice for the real thing, so aunt Beda in the back can hear you too.
One more time, a little louder.
Maria Eva Sundström.
...Maria Eva Sundström
as your lawfully wedded wife?
-Yes.
-And then we reverse it so it's your turn.
And then the mandatory kiss.
Badabing, badabong.
and then the mandatory kiss.
Till death do you part. Done.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
She's just nervous, for sure.
Go talk to her and then come back.
-This happens all the time. All the time.
-Mia!
Oh my, oh my God.
Mia!
Frida! Frida!
-So lucky, I thought you had left.
-Mia, I can't do this.
I just left Tim in the church.
I can't marry him. I'm in love with you.
But you're not done with him.
You're not done with your life together.
What happened today, when I sat there waiting for you because you were with him.
It will be like that all the time, won't it?
I needed to wake up from this dream
with you and today I did.
-Don't you understand what I sacrificed for us?
-Jesus Christ, you're not the only one making sacrifices.
This isn't just about you.
-Frida, please, don't go.
-But you're not fighting for this.
-Yes I am, I'm here now.
-No, you're not!
Frida, don't go. Frida!
It's the wedding menus.
They just came.
Done. Some timing.
-I've looked everywhere for you.
-I have nothing to say to you.
But I am thinking about what
to say to our families and our friends.
"Regrettably, the wedding is cancelled."
"Mia is apparently a dyke."
How do you...how do you know?
I saw you and Frida.
You fucking asshole.
I'm sorry you found out about it like this.
Get out of here, damn it.
Get the hell out of here, damn it!
-Tim...
-Leave, damn it! Leave!
I think the biggest reason Tim and I were getting married
was that everyone was expecting us to.
Are you ashamed of me?
I just want you to be happy and healthy.
-Do you think it's my fault?
-Why does it have to be anyone's fault?
Why Frida?
Because I love her.
Seven years, Mia.
Seven years.
I thought I knew who I was building a life with.
I am so sorry, Tim.
You don't exist to me anymore.
I'm going to Skåne with dad.
I'll move out when I get back.
-Hi.
-Is Frida here?
-No, she's not here.
-Do you know where she is?
Are you Mia?
-Can you tell me where she is?
-Not on your life.
Where is Frida?
Elisabeth, do you know where she is?
She needs peace and quiet, Mia.
And you're not exactly what I'd call peace and quiet to her right now.
I have made a complete fool of myself, don't you understand that?
I have nothing left.
If you know where she is,
please tell me - now.
I really hope you know what you're doing.
Let me see.
Her flight to Barcelona leaves in 40 minutes.
Now go.
Flight DY3656 to Barcelona
is departing from Gate 7.