-I'm going home with you.
-Home?
-I thought you were staying for a week?
-Yes, but I changed my mind.
Coming back home really isn't your thing, is it.
Aren't you bringing her flower inside?
She gave you such a lovely vase.
It's not a flower.
It's an orchid.
And it's been standing here
for 30 years, Elisabeth.
You know, if you spent half as much time
caring about your family as you do your orchids-
-things would probably be different.
-Maybe you should say goodbye to Oskar?
-Ssh! I just want to go home.
God, it feels so good to be home!
If I ever want to go back,
remind me of this trip.
What happened there?
I ran into a branch on the island.
City kid, you know.
-I need to go to the office for a bit now.
-No, don't bother. Take care of it tomorrow.
What is it?
I love you.
I love you, Tim.
Plastic headboards. We'd need to do something
about these floors, I think.
A fireplace.
-I've always wanted one.
-It would be nice in winter.
-But Jakobsberg?
-What's wrong with Jakobsberg?
It's so dull out there.
We would have to redo the whole floor.
And when you get pregnant,
we won't even have room for a nursery.
"When I get pregnant". That could take ages.
Not if you stop taking birth control.
It would take a year to a year and a half.
-What do you mean, I don't want kids now. You know that.
-Maybe not now now.
But in the near future.
You do want kids with me?
We are getting married, right?
-If we're having kids, then that requires planning!
-Tim you can't plan everything. It doesn't work that way.
Well then, how do things work?
Explain to me how things work!
Hey, I'm sorry about yesterday.
You're right.
It makes me panic when you're deciding everything.
Can't you see how stressful it is?
-Well, you need someone to keep you in line.
-What did you say?
Check out Oskar.
He's coming here on Thursday.
He's grown some kind of mustache.
He looks insane. He looks like a psychopath, doesn't he?
This is Tim.
Frida?
It's very empty and lonely here.
Can't you come over here?
I'm coming. I'm coming.
No...
-What?
-Well... I don't know.
It's like you've been on another planet these past two weeks.
I barely recognize you.
What is it?
I will leave you alone.
-You want come over for dinner with us tonight?
-Eh, I can't.
How come you never come over for dinner anymore?
-Did something happen?
-No.
-But, Frida, what's going on?
-Well, I don't know how to say this.
-Me and Mia, we...
-Mia?
Something happened
between her and me.
Something?
Please try to explain, would you.
I think Mia is bisexual,
but I don't think she wants to see it that way.
And what the hell is that supposed to mean?
That I'm in love with her.
Oh dear lord!
I asked you to be nice to her,
not fall in love with her!
-Well then I misunderstood you completely because falling in love with her was my plan all along.
-How the hell can you be joking about something like this?
You can love whoever you want,
but not Lasse's daughter, do you get it?
-Anyone, but not her!
-What am I supposed to do? I'm not exactly proud of myself right now.
-And Elin?
-She doesn't know, but she gets it.
After you've been put through the exact same thing yourself.
Maybe you remember how devastated you were?
And now you're putting Elin through the exact same thing.
Damn that's low, Frida.
-What were you thinking?
-I haven't been thinking.
No, you haven't been.
No...
No, I've never cheated and I never will.
I can't think of anything worse.
Are you at home?
I waited for you for over an hour.
I'm sorry, I got late.
I missed you.
What is it?
-I can't.
-What?
What...?
I hate doing this to you so much.
Who is it?
It's Mia, Oskar's sister.
It must be hard for Lasse having two dykes in the family.
Since he's had such a hard time with us.
I'm in love with her.
So you've been cheating on me with Mia,
who is getting married to her boyfriend.
What the hell are you doing?
Well, I really don't want to do this to you.
I know exactly what you're feeling right now.
I understand.
You know what the most disgusting part is?
I really thought you were better than this.
You're just an experiment to her.
She's never going to leave him.
Do you get that?
Yes. It's... Someone was hung over
when they treaded this.
Give me the glass!
Now tell me about the mustache.
It's some kind of age crisis?
I don't know, it just happened.
Tim was totally freaked out.
He said I had to shave it off
if I wanted to be his best man.
Can I kidnap him this weekend?
Drag him to the archipelago. A bachelor's party or something.
Sure, do that.
-Have you heard from dad by the way?
-Yes, everything's fine.
-You haven't heard from him?
-No.
OK.
I'm meant to say hi from Frida by the way.
She's here this weekend with her school.
She's doing a concert at Östra Real.
You can hang out then. It's cool.
-I talked to Frida.
-Hm. She's all good?
-Not really actually.
-Oh.
-She is in love with your daughter.
-What did you say?
-Come again?
-From what I gather, Mia has feelings for Frida too.
-But Mia is engaged to Tim.
-Of course I know that, but...
-So maybe she's bisexual.
-No, I don't think so.
-Let's eat now. Sit down.
-Are you kidding?
Haricot verts?
So it's OK that my daughter is gay,
but not Mia?
My daughter is not homosexual,
Elisabeth.
-Maybe you think it's wrong, maybe you think it's a bit disgusting?
-Did I say that?
-But it's not completely normal, right?
-No, it's not completely fucking normal, is it?
No parents really want their child to be gay or lesbian,
if we're being honest, Elisabeth.
So Frida isn't normal?
Lasse when Frida came out...
...it wasn't easy, I admit.
But today I'm very happy that she is who she is.
That she stands up for who she is.
She wouldn't be my daughter otherwise.
Let's not talk about this anymore. OK?
How would that solve anything?
Lasse?
This is completely insane!
Who the hell are you, really?
What the hell are you thinking right now?
No, God damn it!
Mia?
I shouldn't have come. I have to...I have to go.
Oskar couldn't make it, but he says hi.
Wait, wait, wait, wait...
Just give me five minutes, I'll send
the kids home with their parents.
Wait for me.
Don't go.
I'm so happy you're here.
Did you hide here, or what?
I want to go away with you.
Far away.
Do you want to?
I think you've been lying a little bit to me.
I'm hardly your first girl.
No. Can you tell?
Yes, you could say that.
I thought about it on Fyn too.
Why haven't you told me?
-Are you ashamed?
-No.
I just didn't think I would feel like this again.
Were you in love with her?
-Will it make you jealous if I say yes?
-Eh, yes. Absolutely.
-Does Tim know?
-No.
It was much earlier.
I've never cheated on him.
Until now.
I want to be with you all the time.
I don't want to be just someone you cheat on Tim with.
If I had the choice, I would build a house somewhere by the ocean.
Andalusia.
Or Catalonia.
-I could live with you in a shoe box.
-Seriously?
What if we did.
Just take off, you and me.
And start over somewhere else.
Why can't we start over here?
Is that too realistic for you?
Not romantic enough?
But, Frida...
Frida.
I've never felt as strongly about anyone as I do about you in my entire life.
But you just want to run away all the time.
Start over?
Do you know how much I'd want to do that.
But you're getting married to Tim in three months.
I am so stupid.
What are you doing?
Do you love him?
You can't marry Tim.
I won't be able to handle that.
-Dad, did something happen?
-No, I just wanted to hear your voice.
And...say thank you for the vase I got.
I'm not sure I did.
OK. You're welcome.
-Are you OK??
-Yes, I'm fine.
I woke you up didn't I? I didn't realize
it was this late.
-Let's hang up.
-OK.
Fine.
-Bye then.
-Bye.
We could live like this, couldn't we?
This is almost like a shoe box.
I wouldn't want to live like this.
It's not real.
Shutting ourselves in a room miles away from everything.
It's hard for me, Frida.
I'm not as brave as you.
I just wish we didn't have to be questioned.
I want them to ask.
I'm proud of you.
I want to show everyone how much I like you.
-One o'clock at Mosebacke, then.
-Yes.
Hey.
I don't get any stubble, just some stuff.
I thought it looked OK.
-I think I've known that about Mia the whole time.
-What?
Yes, even though it only was suspicions
I had a hard time dealing with it.
You know, when Frida told me...
...I remember thinking, in a state of panic,
about everything I would miss out on.
You know, wedding, becoming a grandmother,
all those things.
But, hey...now I know better.
Yes.
I just want her to be fine.
-I'm going to the city to take care of some things.
-Now? We're leaving soon.
-What?
-To the church. You're the one who booked the meeting with the pastor at one.
Well, well, you're nervous now, aren't you?
Wedding ceremonies are actually over really quickly.
So I want you to really cherish the moment when you're up here with me.
It goes like this:
first you say your vows to each other.
then I turn to you Tim.
And your full name.
-Tim Aaron Bratthall.
-Tim Aaron, nice name, Bratthall.
-Do you take this...
-Maria.
You'll have to raise your voice for the real thing, so aunt Beda in the back can hear you too.
One more time, a little louder.
Maria Eva Sundström.
...Maria Eva Sundström
as your lawfully wedded wife?
-Yes.
-And then we reverse it so it's your turn.
And then the mandatory kiss.
Badabing, badabong.
and then the mandatory kiss.
Till death do you part. Done.
I can't.
I'm sorry.
She's just nervous, for sure.
Go talk to her and then come back.
-This happens all the time. All the time.
-Mia!
Oh my, oh my God.
Mia!
Frida! Frida!
-So lucky, I thought you had left.
-Mia, I can't do this.
I just left Tim in the church.
I can't marry him. I'm in love with you.
But you're not done with him.
You're not done with your life together.
What happened today, when I sat there waiting for you because you were with him.
It will be like that all the time, won't it?
I needed to wake up from this dream
with you and today I did.
-Don't you understand what I sacrificed for us?
-Jesus Christ, you're not the only one making sacrifices.
This isn't just about you.
-Frida, please, don't go.
-But you're not fighting for this.
-Yes I am, I'm here now.
-No, you're not!
Frida, don't go. Frida!
It's the wedding menus.
They just came.
Done. Some timing.
-I've looked everywhere for you.
-I have nothing to say to you.
But I am thinking about what
to say to our families and our friends.
"Regrettably, the wedding is cancelled."
"Mia is apparently a dyke."
How do you...how do you know?
I saw you and Frida.
You fucking asshole.
I'm sorry you found out about it like this.
Get out of here, damn it.
Get the hell out of here, damn it!
-Tim...
-Leave, damn it! Leave!
I think the biggest reason Tim and I were getting married
was that everyone was expecting us to.
Are you ashamed of me?
I just want you to be happy and healthy.
-Do you think it's my fault?
-Why does it have to be anyone's fault?
Why Frida?
Because I love her.
Seven years, Mia.
Seven years.
I thought I knew who I was building a life with.
I am so sorry, Tim.
You don't exist to me anymore.
I'm going to Skåne with dad.
I'll move out when I get back.
-Hi.
-Is Frida here?
-No, she's not here.
-Do you know where she is?
Are you Mia?
-Can you tell me where she is?
-Not on your life.
Where is Frida?
Elisabeth, do you know where she is?
She needs peace and quiet, Mia.
And you're not exactly what I'd call peace and quiet to her right now.
I have made a complete fool of myself, don't you understand that?
I have nothing left.
If you know where she is,
please tell me - now.
I really hope you know what you're doing.
Let me see.
Her flight to Barcelona leaves in 40 minutes.
Now go.
Flight DY3656 to Barcelona
is departing from Gate 7.